

Dhana Lakshmi Peeta

Under Graduate

An enthusiastic engineering fresher who is a self-starter and capable to use technical skills for the betterment of the organization. Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at University in the last three years.

peetadhanalakshmi@gmail.com

8019614446

CGPA - 9/10

Q Guntur, India

in linkedin.com/in/dhanalakshmipeeta

EDUCATION

RGUKT IIIT SKLM

B-Tech - CSE

2018 - Present

RGUKT IIIT SKLM

PUC(Pre University Course)

2016 - 2018 CGPA - 9.33/10

Oxford IIT Public School

SSC

2016 CGPA - 10/10

PERSONAL PROJECTS

SMART BILLING

 An image of the products placed on the surface will be taken & given as input to system to generate the bill automatically by using Deep learning & computer vision concepts.

ELECTRICITY GENERATION VIA SPEED BEAKERS.

 There is a system to generate power by converting the potential energy generated by a vehicle going up on a speed breaker into kinetic energy and these to electrical energy.

PIRACY PROTECTION IN MOVIE THEATERS

 The proposed system makes use of image processing techniques over an image acquired from a camera mounted at a suitable location over the movie theatre screen.

DONAR-DONY

 A Web Application that acts as a platform for the donors to donate things to Needy.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing & Sales Internship SHIVA VERMA IELTS TRAINING

12/2020 - 01/2021

Data Collection & Data Entry InternSYNXA IT Pvt. Ltd

05/2020 - 06/2020

Internshala Student Partner Intern INTERNSHALA

06/2018 - 08/2018

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

- -> Bagged bronze medal in JHUB HACKATHON 2k19, HYD. Project " Generation of Electricity via speed beakers".
- -> One among the top 20 innovative ideas 2019 by JHUB-Hyderabad. Project "Donar-Dony"& "Smart Trolley".
- -> Secured first place in state level Science Fair
- -> Bagged gold medal in English Olympiad state level.
- -> Secured state 1st in SSC examinations.
- ->Bagged silver medal innovative idea presentation in national level tech fest.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Placement & Training Cell

CSE Department Student Coordinator

MindSpace Club

Lead Member. This club is a platform for students to develop technically.

WORKSHOPS & CERTIFICATES

All these details are in the below attached profile page. https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhanalakshmipeeta

LANGUAGES

English Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency

anish Telug

Elementary Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

